{
    "id": "51b5033b325640d29009f322d8cf3aff",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Granny …………………………. in the afternoon.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about a future event that is already planned.",
            "answers": [
                "arrives",
                "is arriving",
                "has been arriving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… this color.",
            "description": "The verb like is hardly ever used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "am liking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I helped him because I …………………………. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loved",
                "am loving",
                "have loved"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………. married in May.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about a future event that is already planned.",
            "answers": [
                "gets",
                "is getting",
                "will be getting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. that education can liberate all.",
            "description": "Believe is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "believe",
                "am believing",
                "have believed"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. that they are in love.",
            "description": "When feel means have an opinion, it is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "feel",
                "am feeling",
                "have felt"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. how to swim.",
            "description": "Know is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "am knowing",
                "have known"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................ my vacation.",
            "description": "The present continuous is used to talk about ongoing situations.",
            "answers": [
                "enjoy",
                "am enjoying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The children …………………………. when the mother came home.",
            "description": "The past continuous is used to talk about the longer background action that was in progress when another action occurred.",
            "answers": [
                "are playing",
                "played",
                "were playing"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… intelligent.",
            "description": "Look is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "looks",
                "is looking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………… to a family or artisans.",
            "description": "Belong is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "belongs",
                "is belonging"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………………. 100 pounds.",
            "description": "Weigh is not normally used in the continuous form. ",
            "answers": [
                "weighs",
                "is weighing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}